Finding Aid for the Yvar Mikhashoff Collection of Reel to Reel Tapes, 1961-1984
State University of New York at Buffalo. Music Library
- Reel to reel tapes with Mikhashoff as performer or composer, 1961-1984, I.; Item 1-123
  - Yvar Mikhashoff Collection of Reel to reel tapes, Tape 100, 1981-03-21, 1 7 inch reel; Container title: 1981 Copland Concert #3 Performers: University Philharmonia of SUNY Buffalo, James Kasprowicz, conductor; Mikhashoff, piano; Leo Smit, piano; Gary Burgess, tenor Recording location: Albany Institute, Albany, New York Program titled Copland and Smit; world première: Variations for piano and small orchestra; arranged by Mikhashoff: Three pieces for young performers, set II; the beginning of this concert is on Tape 99 Derivative files created: 7 (Box 7, Item 100)
    Contents: Copland: Old American songs, set I. Songs 2-6 -- Three pieces for young performers, set I; Smit: Variations for piano and small orchestra; Copland: Three pieces for young performers, set II -- Appalachian spring
    Preservation archival master file(s): ubmu0001_4_100_01am.wav
    Production master files file: ubmu0001_4_100_01-01pm.wav, ubmu0001_4_100_01-02pm.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0001_4_100_01-01sc.mp3, ubmu0001_4_100_01-02sc.mp3
  - Yvar Mikhashoff Collection of Reel to reel tapes, Tape 101, 1981-03-22, 1 7 inch reel; Container title: 1981 Copland Concert #4 Performers: Mikhashoff, piano; Leo Smit, piano; Thomas Halpin, violin Recording location: Albany Institute, Albany, New York Photocopy of printed program for concert titled Copland goes South, the 4th concert in a Copland festival. On container: "Guarnieri - Copland (minus Sonata)" Derivative files created: 4 (Box 7, Item 101)
    Contents: Guarnieri: Ponteio; Villa-Lobos: Polichinelle; Ginastera: Tribute to Villa-Lobos -- Tribute to J.J. Castro -- Tribute to Aaron Copland; Orrego-Salas: Pastoral and scherzo; Copland: Danzon cubano
    Preservation archival master file(s): ubmu0001_4_101_01am.wav
    Production master files file: ubmu0001_4_101_01-01pm.wav, ubmu0001_4_101_01-02pm.wav, ubmu0001_4_101_01-03pm.wav, ubmu0001_4_101_01-04pm.wav, ubmu0001_4_101_01-05pm.wav, ubmu0001_4_101_01-06pm.wav, ubmu0001_4_101_01-07pm.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0001_4_101_01-01sc.mp3, ubmu0001_4_101_01-02sc.mp3, ubmu0001_4_101_01-03sc.mp3, ubmu0001_4_101_01-04sc.mp3, ubmu0001_4_101_01-05sc.mp3, ubmu0001_4_101_01-06sc.mp3, ubmu0001_4_101_01-07sc.mp3
  - Yvar Mikhashoff Collection of Reel to reel tapes, Tape 102, 1981-07-22, 1 7 inch reel; Container title: Jazzy 20's, 7/22/81, Indian Hill, Stockbridge Performers: Mikhashoff, piano; Thomas Halpin, violin; Douglas Bish, clarinet; Anthony de Mare, piano Recording location: Brown Room, Indian Hill, Boston University Tanglewood Institute According to the program, the Krenek is on Side 1, the 1st half of the concert on Side 2 - please restore to concert order Photocopy of printed program inserted for concert titled The jazzy 20s: Hits by Antheil, Copland, Krenek and Stravinsky; Krenek suite transcribed and arranged by Mikhashoff Derivative files created: 1 (Box 7, Item 102)
    Contents: Copland: Ukele Serenade; Stravinsky: Suite from 'Histoire du Soldat'; Antheil: Sonata no.2 for violin and piano; Krenek: Johnny's jazz band. Suite from the opera Jonny spielt auf
    Preservation archival master file(s): ubmu0001_4_102_01am.wav, ubmu0001_4_102_02am.wav
    Production master files file: ubmu0001_4_102_01-01pm.wav, ubmu0001_4_102_01-02pm.wav, ubmu0001_4_102_01-03pm.wav, ubmu0001_4_102_02-01pm.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0001_4_102_01-01sc.mp3, ubmu0001_4_102_01-02sc.mp3, ubmu0001_4_102_01-03sc.mp3, ubmu0001_4_102_02-01sc.mp3
  - Yvar Mikhashoff Collection of Reel to reel tapes, Tape 103, 1981-10-11, 1 7 inch reel; Container title: Jonny spielt auf / Buffalo Performers: Mikhashoff, piano; Thomas Halpin, violin; Allen Sigel, clarinet Recording location: University at Buffalo, Baird Recital Hall Photocopy of program inserted; transcribed and arranged by Mikhashoff 1 file, 1 work. Includes spoken introduction Derivative files created: 2 (Box 7, Item 103)
    Contents: Krenek: Jonny spielt auf
    Preservation archival master file(s): ubmu0001_4_103_01am.wav
    Production master files file: ubmu0001_4_103_01-01pm.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0001_4_103_01-01sc.mp3
  - Yvar Mikhashoff Collection of Reel to reel tapes, Tape 104, 1981-10-11, 1 7 inch reel; Container title: Krenek Jonny Performers: Mikhashoff, piano; Thomas Halpin, violin; Allen Sigel, clarinet Recording location: University at Buffalo, Baird Recital Hall Recorded on two sides - check contents (see comments) Contents from container. The original processor included the first 4 works on the program but not stated on the container; Program titled Tribute to Ernst Krenek; Jonny's Jazz Band (world première) was transcribed and arranged by Mikhashoff; Ernst Krenek, guest composer, was present for this tribute Derivative files created: 4 (Box 7, Item 104)
    Contents: Krenek: Trio for violin, clarinet and piano -- Jonny's jazz band: Suite from the opera "Jonny spielt auf"
    Preservation archival master file(s): ubmu0001_4_104_01am.wav, ubmu0001_4_104_02am.wav
    Production master files file: ubmu0001_4_104_01-01pm.wav, ubmu0001_4_104_02-01pm.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0001_4_104_01-01sc.mp3, ubmu0001_4_104_02-01sc.mp3
  - Yvar Mikhashoff Collection of Reel to reel tapes, Tape 105, 1981-10-11, 1 7 inch reel; Container title: Tribute to Ernst Krenek, Oct. 11, 1981. Jonny spielt auf: Suite: Last half of program Performers: Mikhashoff, piano; Thomas Halpin, violin; Allen Sigel, clarinet Recording location: University at Buffalo, Baird Recital Hall Photocopy of printed program inserted for concert titled Tribute to Ernst Krenek; suite transcribed and arranged by Mikhashoff. Note on container about clarinet being "off" in either no. 8 or 5 (Side B?). 1 work, 4 files Derivative files created: 4 (Box 7, Item 105)
    Contents: Krenek: Jonny spielt auf Suite
    Preservation archival master file(s): ubmu0001_4_105_01am.wav, ubmu0001_4_105_02am.wav
    Production master files file: ubmu0001_4_105_01-01pm.wav, ubmu0001_4_105_01-02pm.wav, ubmu0001_4_105_02-01pm.wav, ubmu0001_4_105_02-02pm.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0001_4_105_01-01sc.mp3, ubmu0001_4_105_01-02sc.mp3, ubmu0001_4_105_02-01sc.mp3, ubmu0001_4_105_02-02sc.mp3
  - Yvar Mikhashoff Collection of Reel to reel tapes, Tape 106, 1981-04-30, 1 7 inch reel; Container title: Numus Festival Aarhus April 30, 1981 Performers: Mikhashoff, piano Recording location: Katedralskolens Festsal, Aarhus, Denmark Photocopy of printed program inserted; World premières: Preludes, Discourse on time Derivative files created: 1 (Box 7, Item 106)
    Contents: Wolff: Preludes for piano; Norholm: Discourse on time; Rzewski: Four pieces: IV; Ives: Sonata no.2 'Concord, Mass. 1840-60'
    Preservation archival master file(s): ubmu0001_4_106_01am.wav
    Production master files file: ubmu0001_4_106_01-01pm.wav, ubmu0001_4_106_01-02pm.wav, ubmu0001_4_106_01-03pm.wav, ubmu0001_4_106_01-04pm.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0001_4_106_01-01sc.mp3, ubmu0001_4_106_01-02sc.mp3, ubmu0001_4_106_01-03sc.mp3, ubmu0001_4_106_01-04sc.mp3
  - Yvar Mikhashoff Collection of Reel to reel tapes, Tape 107, 1981-09-20, 1 7 inch reel; Container title: James Willey: A prayer after all Performers: Mikhashoff, piano Recording location: Doty Auditorium, SUNY College of Arts and Sciences at Geneseo Label on back of container states that only the Willey work is on the tape, not the other 4 works played on the concert; printed program inserted Derivative files created: 1 (Box 7, Item 107)
    Contents: Willey: A prayer after all
    Preservation archival master file(s): ubmu0001_4_107_01am.wav
    Production master files file: ubmu0001_4_107_01-01pm.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0001_4_107_01-01sc.mp3
  - Yvar Mikhashoff Collection of Reel to reel tapes, Tape 108, 18 April 1982?, 1 7 inch reel; Container title: Foss - Ni Bruit, Ni Vitesse Performers: Mikhashoff, piano; Jan Williams, percussion; Thomas Halpin, violin Recording location: Albright-Knox Art Gallery, Buffalo, New York Check contents - see comments Photocopy of printed program inserted for concert titled An evening with Lukas Foss although the origin of the tape is not certain. It could contain the a performance of the piece, the entire concert, or the tape part needed for duo performance of the composition. Mikhashoff and Williams performed the piece twice in 1982 (Paris and Buffalo); for both performances they needed a tape part; a description of the piece can be found in Foss: A bio-bibliography (Perone, 1991). See W79 in this book for alternate possible performance dates. The composition is written for 2 pianists and 2 percussionists or, alternatively, for pianist, percussionist, and tape. Derivative files created: 16 (Box 8, Item 108)
    Contents: Foss: Ni bruit, ni vitesse
    Preservation archival master file(s): ubmu0001_4_108_01am.wav
    Production master files file: ubmu0001_4_108_01-01pm.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0001_4_108_01-01sc.mp3
  - Yvar Mikhashoff Collection of Reel to reel tapes, Tape 109, 1982-06-06, 1 10.5 inch reel; Container title: Holland Festival #3 Performers: Mikhashoff, pianist, spoken introductions to composers Recording location: De Doelen, Rotterdam, Netherlands Photocopy of printed program inserted for concert titled American piano with brief composer introductions by Mikhashoff before every work; world première of Nancarrow's Sonatina for piano; Holland Festival 1982: Concert No. 3; radio broadcast on 14 October 1982 Derivative files created: 12 (Box 8, Item 109)
    Contents: Cowell: Advertisement; Ives: Alcotts; Ornstein: A la chinoise; Griffes: The white peacock; Gershwin: Rialto ripples; Copland: Three moods; Antheil, George: Sonata no.3, "The death of machines"; Cowell: The banshee; Thomson: Five easy pieces; Rudhyar: Stars and sunburst; Nancarrow: Sonatina for piano; Becker: Sound piece no.5; Bernstein: Two anniversaries; Antheil: Valentine waltz; Riegger: Tone clusters; Feldman: Illusions; Hiller: Blue triangle; Barber: Fugue
    Preservation archival master file(s): ubmu0001_4_109_01am.wav, ubmu0001_4_109_02am.wav
    Production master files file: ubmu0001_4_109_01_01pm.wav, ubmu0001_4_109_01_02pm.wav, ubmu0001_4_109_01_03pm.wav, ubmu0001_4_109_01_04pm.wav, ubmu0001_4_109_01_05pm.wav, ubmu0001_4_109_01_06pm.wav, ubmu0001_4_109_01_07pm.wav, ubmu0001_4_109_01_08pm.wav, ubmu0001_4_109_01_09pm.wav, ubmu0001_4_109_01_10pm.wav, ubmu0001_4_109_02_01pm.wav, ubmu0001_4_109_02_02pm.wav, ubmu0001_4_109_02_03pm.wav, ubmu0001_4_109_02_04pm.wav, ubmu0001_4_109_02_05pm.wav, ubmu0001_4_109_02_06pm.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0001_4_109_01_01sc.mp3, ubmu0001_4_109_01_02sc.mp3, ubmu0001_4_109_01_03sc.mp3, ubmu0001_4_109_01_04sc.mp3, ubmu0001_4_109_01_05sc.mp3, ubmu0001_4_109_01_06sc.mp3, ubmu0001_4_109_01_07sc.mp3, ubmu0001_4_109_01_08sc.mp3, ubmu0001_4_109_01_09sc.mp3, ubmu0001_4_109_01_10sc.mp3, ubmu0001_4_109_02_01sc.mp3, ubmu0001_4_109_02_02sc.mp3, ubmu0001_4_109_02_03sc.mp3, ubmu0001_4_109_02_04sc.mp3, ubmu0001_4_109_02_05sc.mp3, ubmu0001_4_109_02_06sc.mp3
  - Yvar Mikhashoff Collection of Reel to reel tapes, Tape 110, 1982-06-04, 1 10.5 inch reel; Container title: Holland Fest #5 Performers: Mikhashoff, piano; CalArts Twentieth-Century Players; Daniel Shulman, conductor Recording location: De Doelen, Rotterdam, Netherlands Concert no.5 of Holland Festival 1982; radio broadcast on 29 October 1978; detailed transcription of the concert timings laid in container; one page photocopy of Bennett Lerner world première recording laid in container Derivative files created: 6 (Box 8, Item 110)
    Contents: Anonymous: Low dutch tune; Peter: Quintet no.6; Hagen: Adams and Washington; Jackson: Dirge and dead march; Reinagle: Indian march; Traditional: Fife and drum medley; Carr: The siege of Tripoli; Heinrich: Tower of Babel; Farwell: Dawn: Fantasy on Indian themes; Ives: Holiday quickstep; Griffes: Sketch on Indian themes; Ives: Halloween -- Country band march; Joplin: The ragtime dance
    Preservation archival master file(s): ubmu0001_4_110_01am.wav
    Production master files file: ubmu0001_4_110_01-01pm.wav, ubmu0001_4_110_01-02pm.wav, ubmu0001_4_110_01-03pm.wav, ubmu0001_4_110_01-04pm.wav, ubmu0001_4_110_01-05pm.wav, ubmu0001_4_110_01-06pm.wav, ubmu0001_4_110_01-07pm.wav, ubmu0001_4_110_01-08pm.wav, ubmu0001_4_110_01-09pm.wav, ubmu0001_4_110_01-10pm.wav, ubmu0001_4_110_01-11pm.wav, ubmu0001_4_110_01-12pm.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0001_4_110_01-01sc.mp3, ubmu0001_4_110_01-02sc.mp3, ubmu0001_4_110_01-03sc.mp3, ubmu0001_4_110_01-04sc.mp3, ubmu0001_4_110_01-05sc.mp3, ubmu0001_4_110_01-06sc.mp3, ubmu0001_4_110_01-07sc.mp3, ubmu0001_4_110_01-08sc.mp3, ubmu0001_4_110_01-09sc.mp3, ubmu0001_4_110_01-10sc.mp3, ubmu0001_4_110_01-11sc.mp3, ubmu0001_4_110_01-12sc.mp3
  - Yvar Mikhashoff Collection of Reel to reel tapes, Tape 111, 1982-07-06, 1 10.5 inch reel; Container title: Yvar Mikhashoff, piano recital, New Music America '82 Performers: Mikhashoff, piano Recording location: Preston Bradley Hall, Chicago Public Library, Chicago Photocopy of printed program inserted for concert presented at Mayor Byrne's New Music America, Festival 1982; front label on box is from WFMT (Chicago's fine arts station); spine marking is C. Wolff: Preludes but presumably the entire concert is on the tape Derivative files created: 3 (Box 8, Item 111)
    Contents: Becker: Soundpiece no.5; Sellars: Sonata no.2; Curran: For Cornelius; Foss: Solo for piano; Rudhyar: Rite of transcendence; Rzewski: Piano piece no.4
    Preservation archival master file(s): ubmu0001_4_111_01am.wav
    Production master files file: ubmu0001_4_111_01-01pm.wav, ubmu0001_4_111_01-02pm.wav, ubmu0001_4_111_01-03pm.wav, ubmu0001_4_111_01-04pm.wav, ubmu0001_4_111_01-05pm.wav, ubmu0001_4_111_01-06pm.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0001_4_111_01-01sc.mp3, ubmu0001_4_111_01-02sc.mp3, ubmu0001_4_111_01-03sc.mp3, ubmu0001_4_111_01-04sc.mp3, ubmu0001_4_111_01-05sc.mp3, ubmu0001_4_111_01-06sc.mp3
  - Yvar Mikhashoff Collection of Reel to reel tapes, Tape 112, 1961/1984, 1 10.5 inch reel; Container title: No marking Performers: Unknown Recording location: Unknown The original processor noted this as being a recording of Christian Wolff's Preludes from the Chicago performance on Tape 111 but there is no evidence to support this 3 files. Prepared piano - Crumb? Derivative files created: 30 (Box 8, Item 112)
    Contents: Unidentified contents (check against Tape 115: Crumb, Cage, Moran?)
    Preservation archival master file(s): ubmu0001_4_112_01am.wav
    Production master files file: ubmu0001_4_112_01-01pm.wav, ubmu0001_4_112_01-02pm.wav, ubmu0001_4_112_01-03pm.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0001_4_112_01-01sc.mp3, ubmu0001_4_112_01-02sc.mp3, ubmu0001_4_112_01-03sc.mp3
  - Yvar Mikhashoff Collection of Reel to reel tapes, Tape 113, 1984, 1 10.5 inch reel; Container title: 1984 Great American Piano Marathon (1) Performers: Mikhashoff, piano Recording location: Music Factory Festival, Bergen, Norway Reel 1 of 2 Photocopy of printed program inserted for concert titled American piano marathon: seventy works in seven hours from seventy years 1914-1984; The title is assumed from Tape 114 which states it is Tape II; complete contents listed but it is unclear how they are divided on the two reels; scribbled notes on reel: "Katy Davis, [Religern outs], 4-25-83 Andrew Ackenbaum, Jefferson in Retirement, Israelite, Rose Music X". 30 files Derivative files created: 20 (Box 8, Item 113)
    Contents: Ives: The Alcotts (1915); Cowell: Advertisement (1914); Griffes: Preludes (1915); Grainger: Bridal lullaby (1916); Ornstein: Afternoon in Chinatown (1918); Copland: Sonnets and moods (1921); Cowell: The banshee (1923); Antheil: Sonatina and shimmy (1923); Gershwin: Impromptu two keys (1923); Thomson: Two sentimental tangos (1923); Rudhyar: Stars and sunburst (1926); Crawford: Prelude (1928); Rieger: Blue voyage (1929); Copland: Piano variations (1929); Brant: Music for a five-and-dime (1932); Nancarrow: Blues (1932); Cage: Two pieces (1935); Harris: Chopin in the citrus belt (1938); Harrison: Sonata no.3 (1938); Krenek: Five pieces (1938); Thomson: Two spanish portraits (1940); Ruggles: Evocations (1943); Ives: Hawthorne (1941); Eisler: Sonata no.3 (1943); Bernstein: Anniversaries (1943); Beeson: Piano sonata no. 5 (1945); Harris: American ballads (1945); Cage: Suite for toy piano -- In a landscape (1948); Kirchner: Piano sonata (1948); Antheil: Valentine waltzes (1949); Rorem: Barcarolle (1949); Riegger: Tone clusters (1949); Hiller: Blue triangle (1949); Barber: Piano sonata: Allegro (1949); Feldman: Intermission 5 (1952); Wolff: For piano I (1952); Brown: Folio: December 1952 (1952); Cage: Concert (1958); Martino: Piano fantasy (1958); Young: Piano piece for David Tudor I (1960); Gould, Morton: Blues (1963); Hovhaness: Visionary landscapes (1965); Zappa: Piano introduction (1969); Davidovsky: Synchronisms no.6 (1970); Foss: Solo (for Yvar) (1981); Wolff: Prelude (1982); Rudhyar: Processional (1983); Thomson: Portraits (1983); Felder: Rocket summer (1984); Nancarrow: Tango (1984); Leone: Momentum (1984); Shapey: Passacaglia (1984); Cage: Swinging (1984); Vigeland: Three nocturnes (1984); Rzewski: Eggs for Yvar (1984); Curran: Hope street tunnel blues (1984)
    Preservation archival master file(s): ubmu0001_4_113_01am.wav, ubmu0001_4_113_02am.wav
    Production master files file: ubmu0001_4_113_01-01pm.wav, ubmu0001_4_113_01-02pm.wav, ubmu0001_4_113_01-03pm.wav, ubmu0001_4_113_01-04pm.wav, ubmu0001_4_113_01-05pm.wav, ubmu0001_4_113_01-06pm.wav, ubmu0001_4_113_01-07pm.wav, ubmu0001_4_113_01-08pm.wav, ubmu0001_4_113_01-09pm.wav, ubmu0001_4_113_01-10pm.wav, ubmu0001_4_113_01-11pm.wav, ubmu0001_4_113_01-12pm.wav, ubmu0001_4_113_01-13pm.wav, ubmu0001_4_113_01-14pm.wav, ubmu0001_4_113_02-01pm.wav, ubmu0001_4_113_02-02pm.wav, ubmu0001_4_113_02-03pm.wav, ubmu0001_4_113_02-04pm.wav, ubmu0001_4_113_02-05pm.wav, ubmu0001_4_113_02-06pm.wav, ubmu0001_4_113_02-07pm.wav, ubmu0001_4_113_02-08pm.wav, ubmu0001_4_113_02-09pm.wav, ubmu0001_4_113_02-10pm.wav, ubmu0001_4_113_02-11pm.wav, ubmu0001_4_113_02-12pm.wav, ubmu0001_4_113_02-13pm.wav, ubmu0001_4_113_02-14pm.wav, ubmu0001_4_113_02-15pm.wav, ubmu0001_4_113_02-16pm.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0001_4_113_01-01sc.mp3, ubmu0001_4_113_01-02sc.mp3, ubmu0001_4_113_01-03sc.mp3, ubmu0001_4_113_01-04sc.mp3, ubmu0001_4_113_01-05sc.mp3, ubmu0001_4_113_01-06sc.mp3, ubmu0001_4_113_01-07sc.mp3, ubmu0001_4_113_01-08sc.mp3, ubmu0001_4_113_01-09sc.mp3, ubmu0001_4_113_01-10sc.mp3, ubmu0001_4_113_01-11sc.mp3, ubmu0001_4_113_01-12sc.mp3, ubmu0001_4_113_01-13sc.mp3, ubmu0001_4_113_01-14sc.mp3, ubmu0001_4_113_02-01sc.mp3, ubmu0001_4_113_02-02sc.mp3, ubmu0001_4_113_02-03sc.mp3, ubmu0001_4_113_02-04sc.mp3, ubmu0001_4_113_02-05sc.mp3, ubmu0001_4_113_02-06sc.mp3, ubmu0001_4_113_02-07sc.mp3, ubmu0001_4_113_02-08sc.mp3, ubmu0001_4_113_02-09sc.mp3, ubmu0001_4_113_02-10sc.mp3, ubmu0001_4_113_02-11sc.mp3, ubmu0001_4_113_02-12sc.mp3, ubmu0001_4_113_02-13sc.mp3, ubmu0001_4_113_02-14sc.mp3, ubmu0001_4_113_02-15sc.mp3, ubmu0001_4_113_02-16sc.mp3
  - Yvar Mikhashoff Collection of Reel to reel tapes, Tape 114, 1984, 1 10.5 inch reel; Container title: Tape II Great Piano Marathon Master Performers: Mikhashoff, piano Recording location: Music Factory Festival, Bergen, Norway Reel 2 of 2 Photocopy of printed program inserted for concert titled American piano marathon: seventy works in seven hours from seventy years 1914-1984; continuation of Reel 113; complete contents listed but it is unclear how they are divided on the two reels Derivative files created: 3 (Box 8, Item 114)
    Preservation archival master file(s): ubmu0001_4_114_01am.wav, ubmu0001_4_114_02am.wav
    Production master files file: ubmu0001_4_114_01-01pm.wav, ubmu0001_4_114_01-02pm.wav, ubmu0001_4_114_01-03pm.wav, ubmu0001_4_114_01-04pm.wav, ubmu0001_4_114_01-05pm.wav, ubmu0001_4_114_01-06pm.wav, ubmu0001_4_114_01-07pm.wav, ubmu0001_4_114_01-08pm.wav, ubmu0001_4_114_01-09pm.wav, ubmu0001_4_114_01-10pm.wav, ubmu0001_4_114_01-11pm.wav, ubmu0001_4_114_01-12pm.wav, ubmu0001_4_114_01-13pm.wav, ubmu0001_4_114_01-14pm.wav, ubmu0001_4_114_01-15pm.wav, ubmu0001_4_114_01-16pm.wav, ubmu0001_4_114_02-01pm.wav, ubmu0001_4_114_02-02pm.wav, ubmu0001_4_114_02-03pm.wav, ubmu0001_4_114_02-04pm.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0001_4_114_01-01sc.mp3, ubmu0001_4_114_01-02sc.mp3, ubmu0001_4_114_01-03sc.mp3, ubmu0001_4_114_01-04sc.mp3, ubmu0001_4_114_01-05sc.mp3, ubmu0001_4_114_01-06sc.mp3, ubmu0001_4_114_01-07sc.mp3, ubmu0001_4_114_01-08sc.mp3, ubmu0001_4_114_01-09sc.mp3, ubmu0001_4_114_01-10sc.mp3, ubmu0001_4_114_01-11sc.mp3, ubmu0001_4_114_01-12sc.mp3, ubmu0001_4_114_01-13sc.mp3, ubmu0001_4_114_01-14sc.mp3, ubmu0001_4_114_01-15sc.mp3, ubmu0001_4_114_01-16sc.mp3, ubmu0001_4_114_02-01sc.mp3, ubmu0001_4_114_02-02sc.mp3, ubmu0001_4_114_02-03sc.mp3, ubmu0001_4_114_02-04sc.mp3
  - Yvar Mikhashoff Collection of Reel to reel tapes, Tape 115, 1961/1984, 1 10.5 inch reel; Container title: Cage Performers: Mikhashoff? Recording location: Unknown location Annotated as "Copy" Derivative files created: 1 (Box 8, Item 115)
    Contents: Crumb: unspecified work; Cage: unspecified work; Moran: unspecified work
    Preservation archival master file(s): ubmu0001_4_115_01am.wav
    Production master files file: ubmu0001_4_115_01-01pm.wav, ubmu0001_4_115_01-02pm.wav, ubmu0001_4_115_01-03pm.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0001_4_115_01-01sc.mp3, ubmu0001_4_115_01-02sc.mp3, ubmu0001_4_115_01-03sc.mp3
  - Yvar Mikhashoff Collection of Reel to reel tapes, Tape 116, 1961/1984, 1 10.5 inch reel; Container title: Fall of the House Usher Performers: Unknown Recording location: Unknown location Container is signed Roger Meyers; specific durations of part 1 and 2, and timing of voice onset are written on container Derivative files created: 1 (Box 8, Item 116)
    Contents: Mikhashoff: The fall of the house Usher
    Preservation archival master file(s): ubmu0001_4_116_01am.wav
    Production master files file: ubmu0001_4_116_01-01pm.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0001_4_116_01-01sc.mp3
  - Yvar Mikhashoff Collection of Reel to reel tapes, Tape 117, 1961/1984, 1 10.5 inch reel; Container title: Fontana mix Performers: Unknown Recording location: Unknown Check contents Unclear if this is a performance or the electronic tape part, possibly realized by Steve Bradley; the label states: 1 and 3 Cage, 3 and 4 Max Neuhause [sic] Derivative files created: 6 (Box 8, Item 117)
    Contents: Cage: Fontana mix
    Preservation archival master file(s): ubmu0001_4_117_01am.wav
    Production master files file: ubmu0001_4_117_01-01pm.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0001_4_117_01-01sc.mp3
  - Yvar Mikhashoff Collection of Reel to reel tapes, Tape 118, 1961/1984, 1 10.5 inch reel; Container title: Felder, Austin, Sellars, Ligeti, Nancarrow, Daugherty (Enregistrement NAGRA) Performers: Mikhashoff, piano Recording location: Unknown Unspecified works Derivative files created: 1 (Box 8, Item 118)
    Contents: Felder; Austin; Sellars; Ligeti; Nancarrow; Daugherty
    Preservation archival master file(s): ubmu0001_4_118_01am.wav
    Production master files file: ubmu0001_4_118_01-01pm.wav, ubmu0001_4_118_01-02pm.wav, ubmu0001_4_118_01-03pm.wav, ubmu0001_4_118_01-04pm.wav, ubmu0001_4_118_01-05pm.wav, ubmu0001_4_118_01-06pm.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0001_4_118_01-01sc.mp3, ubmu0001_4_118_01-02sc.mp3, ubmu0001_4_118_01-03sc.mp3, ubmu0001_4_118_01-04sc.mp3, ubmu0001_4_118_01-05sc.mp3, ubmu0001_4_118_01-06sc.mp3
  - Yvar Mikhashoff Collection of Reel to reel tapes, Tape 119, 1961/1984, 1 7 inch reel; Container title: Hispania Performers: Mikhashoff?, piano Recording location: Unknown Annotated as "copia" Derivative files created: 3 (Box 8, Item 119)